<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[AllPlayers Dev Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://allplayers.github.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://allplayers.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-08-13T10:45:47-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://allplayers.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[AllPlayers]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://allplayers.github.com">AllPlayers Dev Blog</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regular Expressions and You]]></title>
    <link href="http://allplayers.github.com/blog/2012/08/13/regular-expressions-and-you/"/>
    <updated>2012-08-13T10:05:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://allplayers.github.com/blog/2012/08/13/regular-expressions-and-you</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<iframe src="http://player.vimeo.com/video/47263145" width="500" height="281" frameborder="0" webkitAllowFullScreen mozallowfullscreen allowFullScreen></iframe>


<p> <p><a href="http://vimeo.com/47263145">Eat N Geek 2012-08-09</a></p>

<hr />

<p>Bringing you and Regular Expressions closer to a first base relationship is our beloved <a href="https://twitter.com/jamesiarmes">James Armes</a>. He takes us through the easy, the hard, and the clever, with examples, explanation, and one of the shortest Eat N&#8217; Geeks we have ever sat through. This isn&#8217;t to say that there isn&#8217;t much clear content. It&#8217;s just James is super efficient in drilling it into your brain. You will never see &#8220;Hello World&#8221; quite the same again!</p>

<p>James starts it all off with showing us both simple and complex regular expressions and then leads into telling us about the different types. Turns out, there are at least 4 different types.</p>

<ul>
<li>Simple Regular Expressions</li>
<li>POSIX Basic Regular Expressions</li>
<li>POSIX Extended Regular Expressions</li>
<li>Perl Regular Expressions</li>
</ul>


<p>James focuses mostly on Perl Regular Expressions throughout the talk and toward the end, gives a heads up on what applications and languages use what standard. He also elaborates on the basic characters that make up RegEx, advanced characters, quantifiers, and lazy quantifiers.</p>

<p>Later in the presentation, James presents on more advanced concepts such as grouping, back-referencing, look-aheads, look-behinds, and conditionals. Of all this I personally only knew the first two existed!</p>

<p>Did you know just about every modern computer language has it&#8217;s own implementation of RegEx? James shows us some examples from Javascript, Perl, and PHP.</p>

<p>Lastly, he gives us a look at a couple of tools:</p>

<ul>
<li><a href="http://aurelio.net/txt2regex/">txt2regex</a></li>
<li><a href="http://reggyapp.com/">Reggy (mac)</a></li>
<li><a href="http://regex.larsolavtorvik.com/">One of many web tools</a></li>
</ul>


<p>Check out his resources!</p>

<ul>
<li><a href="http://ex-parrot.com/~pdw/Mail-RFC822-Address.html">Complex email RegEx</a></li>
<li><a href="http://php.net/manual/reference.pcre.pattern.modifiers.php">PHP&#8217;s Extra Modifiers</a></li>
<li><a href="http://search.cpan.org/dist/Regexp-Common/">Perl&#8217;s Regexp::Common library</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.php.net/manual/en/book.pcre.php">PHP&#8217;s Perl Compatible functions</a></li>
<li><a href="http://xkcd.com/208/">xkcd&#8217;s famous RegEx Cartoon</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.regular-expressions.info/">Regular-Expressions.info</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.evernote.com/shard/s124/sh/bd3b424e-f89e-4eb0-a388-cc2a7c44a888/9707ed01c5481a831725344dfb170fe1">James&#8217;s Top Secret Presentation Notes</a> &#8211; Shhhhh. Don&#8217;t tell him I put them here.</li>
</ul>


<iframe src="http://www.slideshare.net/slideshow/embed_code/13925572" width="427" height="356" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no" style="border:1px solid #CCC;border-width:1px 1px 0;margin-bottom:5px" allowfullscreen></iframe>



]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Headless Selenium]]></title>
    <link href="http://allplayers.github.com/blog/2012/08/02/headless-selenium/"/>
    <updated>2012-08-02T14:36:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://allplayers.github.com/blog/2012/08/02/headless-selenium</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Throughout my work here, I (<a href="https://github.com/generalredneck">Allan Chappell</a>) have made strides revamping the way we use Selenium here at AllPlayers. In doing so, I have started a small project on GitHub for a headless implementation of a <a href="https://github.com/generalredneck/headless-selenium">selenium server setup</a> that shows some of how developers here at AllPlayers are not only Open Sourcing our efforts in just the Drupal world, but everywhere we can.</p>

<p>In addition to this, I promote it through <a href="http://generalredneck.com/blog/headless-selenium">my blog</a>. Check it out and feel free to contribute to the efforts of making automated testing easier!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[UNIX wizardry]]></title>
    <link href="http://allplayers.github.com/blog/2012/07/26/unix-wizardry/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-26T13:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://allplayers.github.com/blog/2012/07/26/unix-wizardry</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<iframe src="http://player.vimeo.com/video/46470453" width="500" height="281" frameborder="0" webkitAllowFullScreen mozallowfullscreen allowFullScreen></iframe>


<p> <p><a href="http://vimeo.com/46470453">Eat N Geek 2012-07-26</a></p>

<hr />

<p>This weeks Eat &#8216;N Geek featured <a href="http://twitter.com/bcmiller">Bill Miller</a> - CTO of AllPlayers.com - talking about UNIX &#8220;wizardry&#8221;. Some fun facts: UNIX is a fun-acronym on, during the time, Multics system. The birth of UNIX was shepharded by Ken Thompson and Dennis Ritchie on a PDP-7 to support building their &#8220;space&#8221; game.</p>

<p>The adoption of UNIX, although initially developed at AT&amp;T Bell research labs, was greatly helped by distribution (and adoption) by universities. This is also the reason behind different distributions, such as Berkely&#8217;s BSD (which also plays a heavy role in modern day Mac OSX). From the various distributions, several best practices emerged and the IEEE Posix standard came from best of class of BSD and System V.</p>

<p>Learning a few (or <em>relatively</em> few) commands and &#8220;building blocks&#8221;; the UNIX programs and their interactions provide extremely powerful toolset that is capable of solving many (if not all) problems (and most tools have proven the test of time as well).</p>

<p>Modern day open-source landscape roots itself in the culture of UNIX; Richard Stallman can be particlarly noted for his founding of the Free Software Foundation and perpetuation the culture of the availability and sharing of source code (and the vehement breakdown of any proprietary software).</p>

<p>The <a href="https://docs.google.com/a/allplayers.com/presentation/d/1iqtGnBn0StccUaxVbL8FQNwGp-upDt8U1lcauY1oogo/present#slide=id.g16072346_0_174">attached slides</a> and <a href="http://vimeo.com/46470453">video</a> have a myriad of quick program usage and interactions.</p>

<script async class="speakerdeck-embed" data-id="5015605bb52c6f00020019ca" data-ratio="1.3333333333333333" src="http://allplayers.github.com//speakerdeck.com/assets/embed.js"></script>



]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[AllPlayers Kick-Awesome Podcast 5 - ecommerce marketplaces]]></title>
    <link href="http://allplayers.github.com/blog/2012/07/24/allplayers-kick-awesome-podcast-5-ecommerce-marketplaces/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-24T13:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://allplayers.github.com/blog/2012/07/24/allplayers-kick-awesome-podcast-5-ecommerce-marketplaces</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<iframe width="560" height="315" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/sl652VrO6S0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>


<hr />

<p>During this podcast our resident ecommerce lead: <a href="https://twitter.com/glennpratt">Glenn Pratt</a> discussed the &#8220;ins and outs&#8221; of <a href="http://drupal.org/project/commerce">Drupal commerce</a>, with a particular focus on an ecommerce marketplace.</p>

<p>There&#8217;s a bit of history with the concept of hosting &#8220;marketplaces&#8221;, Drupal has a history with the Ubercart marketplace module. However, in a more general  sense the idea is such that a &#8220;bounded&#8221; group of multiple vendors can sell multiple products (or even the same products). AllPlayers.com use case was such that we wanted to provide a &#8220;store front&#8221; ability to host multiple products per group. We felt Commerce was “built for us” in terms of minimal pre-conceived notions and a lot of flexibility.</p>

<p>In our initial analysis of marketplace implementations, we explored several competion options, such as Magento and Commerce, but the ultimate solution to settle on Drupal Commerce was driven by the flexibility and our domain knowledge in Drupal.</p>

<p>In Drupal the best-practice for &#8220;groups&#8221; is <a href="http://drupal.org/project/og">OG</a> and that is probably the most novel area of AllPlayers.com&#8217;s implementation. There was quite a bit of work to associate OG with the cart and also maintain the integrity of all underlying accounting. We were able to achieve this with minimal &#8220;custom module&#8221; implementation; you can track the &#8220;path to marketplace&#8221; through the <a href="http://drupal.org/node/990204">Drupal issue queue</a>.</p>

<h2>Picks:</h2>

<p>(note: PSR-1/2 accepted)</p>

<ul>
<li>Glenn: <a href="http://astyle.sourceforge.net/">Artistic Style 2.02</a></li>
<li>Allan: <a href="http://drupalladder.org">Drupal Ladder</a> - Get 1% of the community contributing to core</li>
<li>Maksim: <a href="http://dochub.io/">dochub.io</a></li>
<li>David: <a href="http://phptherightway.com">PHP &#8220;the right way&#8221;: community curated PHP best practices</a></li>
<li>Chris: <a href="http://kcpug.org/posts/2012/july-21-2012-todays-thriving-php-ecosystem">KC PHP User&#8217;s Group: &#8220;PHP&#8217;s Thriving Ecosystem&#8221;</a></li>
<li>James: <a href="http://commerceguys.com/webinars/webinar-drupal-8-plug-it-and-go">Commerce Guys D8 plugins webinar</a></li>
</ul>


<h3>Callouts for upcoming events:</h3>

<ul>
<li><a href="http://cposc.org">Central Pennsylvania Open Source Conference</a></li>
<li><a href="http://dallasdrupal.org">Dallas Drupal Days</a></li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Dive Into Baseball]]></title>
    <link href="http://allplayers.github.com/blog/2012/07/22/a-dive-into-baseball-statistics/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-22T11:01:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://allplayers.github.com/blog/2012/07/22/a-dive-into-baseball-statistics</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<iframe width="560" height="315" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/X1Dzn_36bv4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>


<h3>Links</h3>

<ul>
<li><a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_most_watched_television_broadcasts">Links of Most Watched TV Broadcasts</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.baseball-reference.com">Baseball Reference</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.baseballamerica.com/today">Baseball America</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.fangraphs.com/">Fan Graphs</a></li>
<li><a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/PECOTA">PECOTA</a></li>
<li><a href="http://egrandslam.com/">EGrandSlam</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.baseballprospectus.com/">Baseball Prospectus</a></li>
<li><a href="http://mlb.mlb.com/mlb/gameday/index.jsp?gid=2012_07_22_chamlb_detmlb_1&amp;mode=gameday">MLB GameDay</a></li>
<li><a href="http://brooksbaseball.net">Brooks Baseball</a></li>
</ul>


<p>Today for our weekly EatN&#8217;Geek our project manager, Brooks Burton, took us on a dive into the world of baseball and baseball statistics. Following is a reflection on his presentation as well as a summary.</p>

<p>I&#8217;m not going to dive deep into the statistics in this post. If you want to learn about those, Brooks describes them much better in his presentation than I could ever do in a post.  I highly recommend you watch the video and check out the accompanying links on the bottom.</p>

<p>I believe it&#8217;s worthwhile to give a few sentences about my personal background and experiences with baseball in order to give some context to this post.  Since 2006, I have lived in Chicago in a less - than - comfortable proximity to the Chicago Cubs, Wrigely Field, and all the subsequent drunkenness and idiocy that it brings about. The obnoxious fans would always take up my parking spots, and oftentimes planning revolved around checking the Cubs schedule. Granted, I definitely enjoyed Wrigleyville in my college years, but it can get very old very fast.</p>

<p>After living in or close to Wrigleyville, better known as Chicago&#8217;s Frathouse, it&#8217;s fairly understandable why I have come to disrespect baseball and especially its fans.  However, after the presentation I learned that there is much more to baseball, and sports in general, than one (or at least I) can see at first glance.</p>

<p>Traditionally people around the world have cared more about sports than things they <em>should</em> care about.  And why not? Sports has the ability to bring people together across societal boundaries such as wealth, status, employment, and many others.  It&#8217;s one of the few things left in our modern lives that we can truly become passionate about, break ice over, and have discussions about without worrying about political correctness.</p>

<p>In addition, baseball as a sport that&#8217;s deeply rooted in American culture has its own draw.  There&#8217;s something very special about going to a baseball stadium - a certain feel of history and nostalgia of the many games previously played there. In addition, each stadium has different field dimensions bringing its own subtle influence and gently helping some players play their best, while hindering the performance of others.</p>

<p>There are typically two types of fans, or rather two sides of the spectrum. There&#8217;s the Viewer Fan - he watches a few games a season and simply enjoys the game and the atmosphere as it&#8217;s being played. The Geek Fan, on the other hand, analyzes numbers, statistics and almost takes on the role of an amateur general manager.  Newspapers have catered to such fans as early as October 1845 by printing box scores in the sports section.  However, today we have many more stastics and advanced ways of storing them, retrieving them and interacting with them.</p>

<p>The American baseball arena today has a very unique organization structure not found in many other sports.  The MLB umbrella contains two leagues - American League and National League. These two leagues have slight deviations in their rulebooks, and which rules are used when the two leagues clash in the world series is determined by whose stadium the game is played in.</p>

<p>Below the major league teams lies an advanced minor league structure not found in any other sports. A major league team, let&#8217;s take those annoying Cubs for example, will have 25 players. Below those, they will keep track of 10 or so minor league teams to see if they can move them up to the majors once they become good enough. Decisions like these are influenced by relatively advanced statistics such as WAR - Wins Above Replacement.  It&#8217;s an advanced statistics calculation that answers the question &#8220;If I get rid of this player, and replace him with an average player, how many wins will I lose?&#8221;.</p>

<p>Another thing that struck me and gave me quite a bit more respect for baseball was its appreciation of tradition in the face of advanced technology.  While other sports have moved to use technology to increase the accuracy of judgement calls, baseball has stayed away from that.  There are some pretty advanced technological marvels used during games. PITCHFX has cameras that will take up to 60 pictures between when the ball leaves the pitcher&#8217;s hand and when the hitter hits it, determining the trajectory of the ball. After the hit, trajectory tracking systems will capture up to 6000 data points to determine how the ball flew.  However, all this data collection and advanced information technology are <strong>not</strong> used to increase the accuracy of the umpire&#8217;s calls. The umpire always has the final say.  However, when the game is over the umpire can go back to look at the information to learn from his mistakes.</p>

<p>Baseball is a very interesting game wrapped in tradition and nostalgia, refusing to move away from the old, yet managing to adapt to the new in unique ways.  I know I&#8217;ll be going to see a baseball game this summer (I still dislike the Cubs, but the Sox I&#8217;ll definitely go and see).  And I know as I watch the ball fly from player to player on the field that while there&#8217;s a ton of tracking information being collected, at the end of the day, the game is played no different than it was 100 years ago.  And there&#8217;s definitely something cool about that.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Information Security Breach - Wikileaks Scandal]]></title>
    <link href="http://allplayers.github.com/blog/2012/07/12/information-security-breach-wikileaks-scandal/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-12T19:02:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://allplayers.github.com/blog/2012/07/12/information-security-breach-wikileaks-scandal</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<iframe width="560" height="315" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/YMK1GXnQFb0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>


<p>Melissa McKay, wife of the CEO of AllPlayers.com, Jason McKay, indulges us with her hobby of International Security. Her talk is specifically about the content that was released on the Wikileaks website and a brief overview of those involved as well as some known specifics about Government Security Protocol when it comes to technology.</p>

<p>I&#8217;d hate to spoil the video with a long drawn out explanation of what she went over. Definitely worth watching!</p>

<h3>Links</h3>

<ul>
<li><a href="http://firedoglake.com/merged-manning-lamo-chat-logs/">Merged Manning-Lamo Chat Logs</a> - I&#8217;d pay particular attention to May 25</li>
<li><a href="http://www.pbs.org/wgbh/pages/frontline/wikileaks/manning-facebook-page/">Manning&#8217;s Facebook Page</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.pbs.org/wgbh/pages/frontline/wikileaks/">Full Frontline Video</a></li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[AllPlayers Kick-Awesome Podcast 4 - Google Drive - Hangout, Booth Babes, and Code Standards]]></title>
    <link href="http://allplayers.github.com/blog/2012/06/07/allplayers-podcast-4-google-drive-hangout/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-07T08:57:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://allplayers.github.com/blog/2012/06/07/allplayers-podcast-4-google-drive-hangout</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Once again, join the gang as Allan, Chris, James, and Max cover a large spread of multiple topics.</p>

<p>The AllPlayer&#8217;s team starts using Google Hangout to record the podcast as a video and are really impressed with it&#8217;s features and all the fun. Unfortunately, the office network died during the picks of the week causing Google to put up the &#8220;We are having technical difficulty screen&#8221; leaving Max and part of Chris&#8217;s picks lost in a void. See them below though!</p>

<p>The group goes over briefly the use of Google Drive as a means to store documentation for the company.</p>

<p>Max brings up a passionate subject that gets the whole team debating as Allan tries to play Devil&#8217;s Advocate for his own personal jollies.</p>

<p>Lastly, James explains PSR1 and PSR2 and the importance of code standards.</p>

<p>Enjoy!</p>

<p><a href='http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1fhYdn0WuO4' rel="enclosure">AllPlayers Kick-Awesome Podcast #4</a></p>

<h2>Links from the show</h2>

<ul>
<li><a href="http://drupaldork.com/2012/05/lets-talk-about-sex">Booth babes</a></li>
<li>Code Standards

<ul>
<li><a href="https://github.com/pmjones/fig-standards/blob/psr-1-style-guide/proposed/PSR-1-basic.md">PSR1</a></li>
<li><a href="https://github.com/pmjones/fig-standards/blob/psr-1-style-guide/proposed/PSR-2-advanced.md">PSR2</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.access-board.gov/sec508/guide/1194.22.htm">Section 508 - Accessibility</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>


<h2>Picks of the week</h2>

<ul>
<li>Allan: <a href="http://www.dedoimedo.com/life/guide-trolling.html">Guide To Trolling</a></li>
<li>Max: <a href="http://johnpolacek.github.com/superscrollorama/">Super Scrolloroma jQuery Plugin</a></li>
<li>Chris: Cheats and gets 2!

<ul>
<li><a href="http://symfony.com/get_started">Symphony Framework</a></li>
<li><a href="http://pinboard.in/u:wimleers/t:ThePerfectJob">The Perfect Job</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>James - Is humble and recycles

<ul>
<li><a href="https://github.com/pmjones/fig-standards/blob/psr-1-style-guide/proposed/PSR-1-basic.md">PSR1</a></li>
<li><a href="https://github.com/pmjones/fig-standards/blob/psr-1-style-guide/proposed/PSR-2-advanced.md">PSR2</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>


<h2>Show hosts</h2>

<ul>
<li>James Armes: <a href="http://drupal.org/user/284457">BassistJimmyJam</a> / <a href="https://twitter.com/jamesiarmes">@jamesiarmes</a></li>
<li>Allan Chappell: <a href="http://drupal.org/user/368854">generalredneck</a> / <a href="https://twitter.com/general_redneck">@general_redneck</a></li>
<li>Chris Christensen: <a href="http://drupal.org/user/595250">christianchristensen</a> / <a href="https://twitter.com/imetchrischris">@imetchrischris</a></li>
<li>Max Pecherskiy: <a href="http://drupal.org/user/801596">MrMaksimize</a> / <a href="https://twitter.com/mrmaksimize">@mrmaksimize</a></li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[AllPlayers Kick-Awesome Podcast #3 - 00110011]]></title>
    <link href="http://allplayers.github.com/blog/2012/04/25/allplayers-kick-awesome-podcast-number-3-00110011/"/>
    <updated>2012-04-25T12:55:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://allplayers.github.com/blog/2012/04/25/allplayers-kick-awesome-podcast-number-3-00110011</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Join Chris, Max, James and Allan from AllPlayers as they discuss Drupal distributions, small applications, how beer makes men smarter and more!</p>

<p><a href="https://s3.amazonaws.com/allplayers/april_23_2012.mp3" title="AllPlayers Kick-Awesome Podcast #3 - 00110011" rel="enclosure">AllPlayers Kick-Awesome Podcast #3 - 0011</a></p>

<h2>Links from the show</h2>

<ul>
<li><a href="http://www.prweb.com/releases/2012/4/prweb9413528.htm">AllPlayers.com Social Site of the Year!!</a></li>
<li><a href="http://drupal.org/project/distributions">Drupal Distributions</a>:

<ul>
<li><a href="http://drupal.org/project/commerce_kickstart">Commerce Kickstart</a></li>
<li><a href="http://drupal.org/project/panopoly">Panopoly</a></li>
<li><a href="http://drupal.org/project/phoenix">Phoenix</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><a href="http://groups.drupal.org/node/226459">CMI Funding Proposal</a></li>
<li><a href="http://articles.nydailynews.com/2012-04-11/news/31326760_1_brain-teasers-researchers-problem">Beer makes men smarter</a></li>
<li><a href="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</a></li>
<li><a href="http://vimeo.com/40677604">AllPlayers.com Eat-N-Geek - JavaScript Essentials by Travis Tidwell</a></li>
<li><a href="http://imetchrischris.com/blog/2011/10/30/drupal-restful-future/">Drupal’s RESTful Future by Chris Christensen</a></li>
<li>Small Applications:

<ul>
<li><a href="http://genghisapp.com/">Genghis</a></li>
<li><a href="http://getsculpin.com/">Sculpin</a></li>
<li><a href="http://10k.aneventapart.com/">10K Apart</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><a href="http://develop.allplayers.com/oauth.html">Develop AllPlayers.com - OAuth</a></li>
<li><a href="http://code.google.com/p/webfinger/">webfinger</a></li>
<li><a href="https://developers.facebook.com/html5/blog/post/2012/02/27/announcing-ringmark--a-mobile-browser-test-suite/">Ringmark</a></li>
</ul>


<h2>Picks of the week</h2>

<ul>
<li>Allan: <a href="http://www.jefflinwood.com/2012/01/drupal-phonegap-podcast-with-jeff-at-modules-unraveled/">Drupal + PhoneGap Podcast with Jeff Linwood</a></li>
<li>Chris: <a href="http://fabien.potencier.org/article/50/create-your-own-framework-on-top-of-the-symfony2-components-part-1">Create your own framework on top of the Symfony2 Components</a></li>
<li>James: <a href="http://drupal.org/drupalgive">/drupalgive Initiative</a> / <a href="http://drupal-association.ideascale.com/">Drupal Association on IdeaScale</a></li>
<li>Max: <a href="https://github.com/adamdbradley/foresight.js">foresight.js</a></li>
</ul>


<h2>Show hosts</h2>

<ul>
<li>James Armes: <a href="http://drupal.org/user/284457">BassistJimmyJam</a> / <a href="https://twitter.com/jamesiarmes">@jamesiarmes</a></li>
<li>Allan Chappell: <a href="http://drupal.org/user/368854">generalredneck</a> / <a href="https://twitter.com/general_redneck">@general_redneck</a></li>
<li>Chris Christensen: <a href="http://drupal.org/user/595250">christianchristensen</a> / <a href="https://twitter.com/imetchrischris">@imetchrischris</a></li>
<li>Max Pecherskiy: <a href="http://drupal.org/user/801596">MrMaksimize</a> / <a href="https://twitter.com/mrmaksimize">@mrmaksimize</a></li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[AllPlayers.com Wins 2012 Blue Drop Award for Best Social Networking Website Built with Drupal]]></title>
    <link href="http://allplayers.github.com/blog/2012/04/19/allplayers-dot-com-wins-2012-blue-drop-award-for-best-social-networking-website-built-with-drupal/"/>
    <updated>2012-04-19T10:40:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://allplayers.github.com/blog/2012/04/19/allplayers-dot-com-wins-2012-blue-drop-award-for-best-social-networking-website-built-with-drupal</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>After more than a month of nominations and community voting, Irving-based <a href="https://www.allplayers.com">AllPlayers.com</a> has been awarded the &#8220;2012 Best Social Networking Website Built with Drupal&#8221; by the <a href="http://bluedropawards.com">Blue Drop Awards</a> in its inaugural season. The prestigious award was given to <a href="https://www.allplayers.com">AllPlayers.com</a> for their group management and administrative website.</p>

<p>“At AllPlayers.com, we are thrilled to receive the award for Best Social Networking Website Built with Drupal from the Drupal Community,” said Jason McKay, CEO of <a href="https://www.allplayers.com">AllPlayers.com</a>. “The award has added significance as Drupal is responsible for some of the most innovative websites online today; the Blue Drop Awards did a fantastic job of conveying that through the nomination process.”</p>

<p>Some of the key elements that made <a href="https://www.allplayers.com">AllPlayers.com</a> stand out are the site developers. <a href="https://www.allplayers.com">AllPlayers.com</a> empowers some of the best Drupal developers in the country and promotes creativity in development and design. Pushing the limits of the Drupal framework and taking the development community beyond the established comfort zone has increased the <a href="https://www.allplayers.com">AllPlayers.com</a> features and usability while at the same time contributing back significant improvements and enhancements to multiple commonly used components.</p>

<p>“There were so many quality entries to the Blue Drop Awards for the Best Social Networking Website Built with Drupal category this year,” said Michael Caccavano, president, Phase2 Technology. “We salute <a href="https://www.allplayers.com">AllPlayers.com</a> for winning among such strong competition.”</p>

<p>Representing more than 630,000 contributors and developers, Drupal is the largest, most active open-source technology community in the world. The <a href="http://bluedropawards.com">Blue Drop Awards</a> were created to promote Drupal to the greater technology community and to recognize innovative, next-generation websites and the companies that built them. With thousands of sites leveraging Drupal, the new awards program was designed to be the first democratic, voter-driven recognition program for Drupal members.</p>

<p>The inaugural Blue Drop Awards were sponsored by veteran Drupal community members, including Volacci, Phase2 Technology, Lingotek, Standing Cloud, Build a Module, Synaptic Blue, ImageX Media, Achieve Internet, Blink Reaction, Gorton Studios and Mediacurrent.</p>

<p>To see the winning projects and check out the other nominated websites please visit <a href="http://bluedropawards.com">Blue Drop Awards</a></p>

<p>For more information on how to volunteer or participate as a sponsor next year, please contact Ben Finklea, CEO, Volacci at (512) 632-4222 or Ben(at)Volacci(dot)com</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[AllPlayers Kick-Awesome Podcast #2 - DrupalCon Denver Wrap-Up]]></title>
    <link href="http://allplayers.github.com/blog/2012/04/12/allplayers-kick-awesome-podcast-number-2-drupalcon-devner-wrap-up/"/>
    <updated>2012-04-12T15:31:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://allplayers.github.com/blog/2012/04/12/allplayers-kick-awesome-podcast-number-2-drupalcon-devner-wrap-up</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Join Chris, Max, David, James and Allan from AllPlayers as they talk about the latest drupal news, how we planned to plan, and much more!</p>

<p>Get it while it&#8217;s hot!</p>

<p><a href="https://s3.amazonaws.com/allplayers/april-2+2012.mp3" title="AllPlayers Kick-Awesome Podcast #2 - DrupalCon Devner Wrap-Up" rel="enclosure">AllPlayers Kick-Awesome Podcast #2 - DrupalCon Devner Wrap-Up</a></p>

<h2>Links from the show</h2>

<ul>
<li><a href="https://github.com/php-fig/fig-standards/blob/master/accepted/PSR-0.md">PSR-0</a></li>
<li><a href="http://us.php.net/namespaces">Namespaces</a></li>
<li><a href="http://symfony.com/components">Symfony Components</a></li>
<li><a href="http://twig.sensiolabs.org/">Twig</a> / <a href="http://drupal.org/node/1441320">Twig in Drupal</a> / <a href="https://github.com/schmittjoh/twig.js">twig.js</a></li>
<li><a href="http://jacine.net/post/19652705220/theme-system">Let’s Do Something About Drupal’s Theme System</a></li>
<li><a href="http://jacine.github.com/drupal/">A draft of proposed components and coding standards for Drupal 8</a></li>
</ul>


<h2>Picks of the week</h2>

<ul>
<li>Allan: <a href="http://blogs.discovermagazine.com/discoblog/2010/09/07/speed-bumps-of-the-future-creepy-optical-illusion-children/">Speed Bumps of the Future: Creepy Optical Illusion Children</a></li>
<li>Chris: <a href="http://blog.ircmaxell.com/2012/03/phps-source-code-for-php-developers.html">PHP&#8217;s Source Code For PHP Developers</a></li>
<li>David: <a href="http://twig.sensiolabs.org/">Twig</a></li>
<li>Max: <a href="http://learndrupal.org/">Learn Drupal</a> / <a href="http://shichuan.github.com/javascript-patterns/">JS Patterns</a></li>
</ul>


<h2>Show hosts</h2>

<ul>
<li>James Armes: <a href="http://drupal.org/user/284457">BassistJimmyJam</a> / <a href="https://twitter.com/jamesiarmes">@jamesiarmes</a></li>
<li>Allan Chappell: <a href="http://drupal.org/user/368854">generalredneck</a> / <a href="https://twitter.com/general_redneck">@general_redneck</a></li>
<li>Chris Christensen: <a href="http://drupal.org/user/595250">christianchristensen</a> / <a href="https://twitter.com/imetchrischris">@imetchrischris</a></li>
<li>David Lanier: <a href="http://drupal.org/user/89512">nadavoid</a> / <a href="https://twitter.com/nadavoid">@nadavoid</a></li>
<li>Max Pecherskiy: <a href="http://drupal.org/user/801596">MrMaksimize</a> / <a href="https://twitter.com/mrmaksimize">@mrmaksimize</a></li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[AllPlayers Kick-Awesome Podcast #1 - Planning To Plan]]></title>
    <link href="http://allplayers.github.com/blog/2012/03/21/allplayers-kick-awesome-podcast-number-1-planning-to-plan/"/>
    <updated>2012-03-21T15:25:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://allplayers.github.com/blog/2012/03/21/allplayers-kick-awesome-podcast-number-1-planning-to-plan</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>So we finally did it! We started a podcast. Join Chris, Max, Travis, David, James and Allan from AllPlayers as they talk about the latest drupal news, how we planned to plan, and much more!</p>

<p>Get it while it&#8217;s hot!</p>

<p><a href="https://s3.amazonaws.com/allplayers/march-12.mp3" title = "AllPlayers Kick Awesome Podcast #1 - Planning to Plan" rel="enclosure">AllPlayers Kick Awesome Podcast #1 - Planning to Plan</a></p>

<h2>Links from the show</h2>

<ul>
<li><a href="http://apps.google.com">Google Apps</a></li>
<li><a href="http://openatrium.com/">Open Atrium</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.bluedropawards.org/">Blue Drop Awards</a></li>
<li><a href="http://jekyllrb.com/">jekyll</a></li>
<li><a href="http://coordino.com/">Coordino</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.yammer.com/">Yammer</a></li>
<li><a href="https://plus.google.com/">Google+</a></li>
</ul>


<h2>Show hosts</h2>

<ul>
<li>James Armes: <a href="http://drupal.org/user/284457">BassistJimmyJam</a> / <a href="https://twitter.com/jamesiarmes">@jamesiarmes</a></li>
<li>Allan Chappell: <a href="http://drupal.org/user/368854">generalredneck</a> / <a href="https://twitter.com/general_redneck">@general_redneck</a></li>
<li>Chris Christensen: <a href="http://drupal.org/user/595250">christianchristensen</a> / <a href="https://twitter.com/imetchrischris">@imetchrischris</a></li>
<li>David Lanier: <a href="http://drupal.org/user/89512">nadavoid</a> / <a href="https://twitter.com/nadavoid">@nadavoid</a></li>
<li>Max Pecherskiy: <a href="http://drupal.org/user/801596">MrMaksimize</a> / <a href="https://twitter.com/mrmaksimize">@mrmaksimize</a></li>
<li>Travis Tidwell: <a href="http://drupal.org/user/98581">travist</a> / <a href="https://twitter.com/softwaregnome">@softwaregnome</a></li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drush tips and tricks + make, dl, .info inject]]></title>
    <link href="http://allplayers.github.com/blog/2012/03/01/drush-notes/"/>
    <updated>2012-03-01T20:00:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://allplayers.github.com/blog/2012/03/01/drush-notes</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><article class="markdown-body"><p>Did some testing with drush tonight and have some tips:</p></p>

<p><a href="http://drupal.org/project/drush">http://drupal.org/project/drush</a> project has nice pear install info:
(note: may need to sudo)</p>




<pre><code>pear channel-discover pear.drush.org
pear install drush/drush-5.0.0 # note: there may be some instability, but seems ok
</code></pre>




<p>(note: drush-5.0.0 has the &#8211;gitinfofile which injects version into .info)</p>


<!-- more -->




<p><a href="http://drupalcode.org/project/drush.git/blob/refs/heads/master:/README.txt#l79">Drush bash completion</a> is probably a handy tool for sbox CLI: <a href="http://drupalcode.org/project/drush.git/blob/refs/heads/master:/drush.complete.sh">http://drupalcode.org/project/drush.git/blob/refs/heads/master:/drush.complete.sh</a>
namely: sourcing the bash completion script e.g.: <code>. /usr/share/php/drush/drush.complete.sh</code>
(this provides tab completion for drush commands)</p>




<p>Drush5 provides an injection to the .info file; an example use of this would be:
<code>drush dl --package-handler=git_drupalorg --gitinfofile uuid</code>
(note: the &#8211;gitinfofile parameter)</p>




<p>(running <strong>.info inject</strong> by default)
Using the drushrc.php (a file to specify specific specific drush options in a config file&#8230;) we can ensure that <code>gitinfofile</code> is enabled by default:
<code>$command_specific['pm-download'] = array('gitinfofile' =&gt; TRUE);</code>
(note: unfortunately drush_make doesn&#8217;t respect the <code>drush dl</code> paradigm &#8230; drush 5 this will be the preferred method)
(note: to get drush to continue reading my rc file I had to do: <code>drush -c ~/.drush/drushrc.php make example.make www</code>)
(tip: to see what is happening with the actual drush commands use debug/verbose: <code>drush --debug --verbose -c ~/.drush/drushrc.php make example.make www</code>)</p>




<p>We can also have specific <strong>drushrc.php</strong> settings <em>per repo</em> to be fancy:
<a href="http://drupalcode.org/project/drush.git/blob/refs/heads/master:/examples/example.drushrc.php#l8">http://drupalcode.org/project/drush.git/blob/refs/heads/master:/examples/example.drushrc.php#l8</a>
and/or
<a href="http://drupalcode.org/project/drush.git/blob/refs/heads/master:/examples/example.drushrc.php#l332">http://drupalcode.org/project/drush.git/blob/refs/heads/master:/examples/example.drushrc.php#l332</a>
(note: I believe this to be a nice way - and the drush recommended way - to organize our alias&#8217; and other drush specific settings.)
(note: to accomplish this I believe minimal setup through Puppet could get things in place - this would be for deployed env. - everything else would have a Readme)</p>




<p>&lt;(soon) deprecated&gt;</p>




<p>For <strong>drush_make .info inject</strong>&#8230; (or running drush 4.5)</p>




<pre><code>cd ~/.drush/drush_make/
# http://drupal.org/node/1302820
wget http://drupal.org/files/drush_make_inject_info.patch
patch -p1 &lt; drush_make_inject_info.patch
</code></pre>




<p>&lt;/deprecated&gt;</p>


<p></article></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
