<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[General | AllPlayers Dev Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://allplayers.github.com/blog/categories/general/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://allplayers.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-04-25T13:28:32-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://allplayers.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[AllPlayers]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://allplayers.github.com">AllPlayers Dev Blog</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[AllPlayers.com Wins 2012 Blue Drop Award for Best Social Networking Website Built with Drupal]]></title>
    <link href="http://allplayers.github.com/blog/2012/04/19/allplayers-dot-com-wins-2012-blue-drop-award-for-best-social-networking-website-built-with-drupal/"/>
    <updated>2012-04-19T10:40:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://allplayers.github.com/blog/2012/04/19/allplayers-dot-com-wins-2012-blue-drop-award-for-best-social-networking-website-built-with-drupal</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>After more than a month of nominations and community voting, Irving-based <a href="https://www.allplayers.com">AllPlayers.com</a> has been awarded the "2012 Best Social Networking Website Built with Drupal" by the <a href="http://bluedropawards.com">Blue Drop Awards</a> in its inaugural season. The prestigious award was given to <a href="https://www.allplayers.com">AllPlayers.com</a> for their group management and administrative website.</p>

<p>“At AllPlayers.com, we are thrilled to receive the award for Best Social Networking Website Built with Drupal from the Drupal Community,” said Jason McKay, CEO of <a href="https://www.allplayers.com">AllPlayers.com</a>. “The award has added significance as Drupal is responsible for some of the most innovative websites online today; the Blue Drop Awards did a fantastic job of conveying that through the nomination process.”</p>

<p>Some of the key elements that made <a href="https://www.allplayers.com">AllPlayers.com</a> stand out are the site developers. <a href="https://www.allplayers.com">AllPlayers.com</a> empowers some of the best Drupal developers in the country and promotes creativity in development and design. Pushing the limits of the Drupal framework and taking the development community beyond the established comfort zone has increased the <a href="https://www.allplayers.com">AllPlayers.com</a> features and usability while at the same time contributing back significant improvements and enhancements to multiple commonly used components.</p>

<p>“There were so many quality entries to the Blue Drop Awards for the Best Social Networking Website Built with Drupal category this year,” said Michael Caccavano, president, Phase2 Technology. “We salute <a href="https://www.allplayers.com">AllPlayers.com</a> for winning among such strong competition.”</p>

<p>Representing more than 630,000 contributors and developers, Drupal is the largest, most active open-source technology community in the world. The <a href="http://bluedropawards.com">Blue Drop Awards</a> were created to promote Drupal to the greater technology community and to recognize innovative, next-generation websites and the companies that built them. With thousands of sites leveraging Drupal, the new awards program was designed to be the first democratic, voter-driven recognition program for Drupal members.</p>

<p>The inaugural Blue Drop Awards were sponsored by veteran Drupal community members, including Volacci, Phase2 Technology, Lingotek, Standing Cloud, Build a Module, Synaptic Blue, ImageX Media, Achieve Internet, Blink Reaction, Gorton Studios and Mediacurrent.</p>

<p>To see the winning projects and check out the other nominated websites please visit <a href="http://bluedropawards.com">Blue Drop Awards</a></p>

<p>For more information on how to volunteer or participate as a sponsor next year, please contact Ben Finklea, CEO, Volacci at (512) 632-4222 or Ben(at)Volacci(dot)com</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
